Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
♫I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart♫
♫Add another hundred
♫Even when you're ready to leap,♫
♫I'll always be ready to love♫
♫I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart♫
♫Again, you're running from me♫
♫Following you around
is making me lonely♫
♫Again, you're mad at me,♫
♫But why do you have to look so lovely?♫
♫Oh Baby♫
♫Told me not to love, but I already fell♫
♫Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well♫
♫Baby, I'm crush on ya♫
♫I need a way to flirt with you, yeah♫
♫I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart♫
♫Add another hundred
♫Even when you're ready to leap,♫
♫I'll always be ready to love♫
♫I'll use a hundred more tricks to win,
win your heart♫
♫Hello there, my darling♫
♫If you were a laundry,♫
♫I'd be your Rinse Charming♫
♫Ready for love,♫
♫I have two shoulders for you to lean over,♫
♫Even though they feel heavy,
carrying my own beauty (Yep)♫
♫I know, I'm just your type, aren't I?♫
♫You're so hot like fire (Huh?!)♫
♫Because my heart burns for you (Right!)♫
♫I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart♫
♫Add another hundred
♫Even when you're ready to leap,♫
♫I'll always be ready to love♫
Baby, I wanna tell you something…
I love you!
♫I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart♫
♫Add another hundred
♫Even when you're ready to leap,♫
♫I'll always be ready to love♫
♫I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart♫
I just want to let you know
that the show that I'm gonna be on
has asked me to shoot in the upcountry.
We're finally
going to spend the night out of town.
Are you okay with that?
Mm, I... I'm fine.
What happened to your mouth?
Then, if I get unconfident,
I'll look at you.
But why would you?
I'm not on the show with you or anything.
That's because I've already
placed my confidence in you.
And I want you to know...
that no matter who you are,
I will always love you.
Hello, Tutor M.
Your top is here.
Ugh!
What's up?
What's up? Hm?
Well, it's just a little weird.
And...
aren't you happy to find out
that Tong is actually me?
Well, it's like, all this time,
I've been rooting for you to win me over.
I know, right?
Though my Moo-Moo
is quite something else.
Fu!
Mm, actually,
I didn't mean to set my name as Tong.
But after you called me that,
I decided to go with it.
What? So where does
the spelling T-O-N-G in our DM
come from then?
It's...
my government name,
which is...
Dong Qingshan.
Dong Qingshan...
Yes, Muying?
Fu...you!
You really tricked me there.
But I have to thank Tutor M;
otherwise, I wouldn't be
cuddling with you like this.
Then...
go back to your room
now that you've had your cuddle.
Can't I spend the night here?
You can't.
You already paid for your room,
so go sleep there.
It's gonna be fine.
I can always afford it.
Can I please spend the night here?
- No...way.
- Please.
Please?
Go back to your room!
Moo-Moo!
"Moo-Moo," my butt.
Now, go.
Come on, get up.
I'm drained...
Hup! Go back to your room!
Alright.
I'm going back.
But next time,
I'll book... a single room!
With a single bed.
Go!
Get up!
Ugh, Fu! Just go back to your room already!
Okay,
I'll go.
Sweet dreams, Moo.
Just go to your room already.
Sweet dreams.
Mr. Fu?
Hello, Fu.
Long time no see!
Hello, Gimm!
Wow, how have you been?
You've grown so much!
You're the one who's grown so much.
So you're the owner
of a big-time hotel now.
My, how kind of Mr. Chalermchai
to send his precious son
to intern
at my hotel for the summer.
Mm...
More like
he doesn't want me to mess around.
With you,
I have someone to keep me in line.
Right,
so when is your father coming back?
I want to show him the new project.
Hm...
It probably won't be long now.
Once things are going more smoothly in France,
he'll probably come back.
Mm...
so I guess that means
he's starting to pave the way for you
to get some experience?
I think so, too.
Oh, as for the new project,
my father told me I can
give you updates directly.
Mm...
Sure thing.
I'll leave it to you.
- Of course.
- We'll see how it goes.
You got it.
These are gifts for you.
- Wow...
- Take them.
Thank you!
You didn't have to do all this.
How could I not?
I can't just come in empty-handed.
Mm, thank you so much.
Your father is doing great, I trust?
Mm, he is.
Gimm, the new intern…
Gimm, Gunklao Tangwatthanakul,
the one and only son of Uncle Chalermchai,
the owner of T Group malls.
You know him?
Mm,
I've known him since we were kids.
He's grown up to be pretty cute.
Gimm Gunklao.
This is his IG.
- Damn!
He has hundreds of thousands of followers?!
As pale as snow,
yummy to the eyes.
Mm.
Speaking of,
this Gimm
is totally Fu's type.
Tiny,
with pale skin
and a Chinese look.
Look at that.
He's got those cute little cheeks, too.
He's just like Moo.
Perfect.
Now,
Fu's gonna stop winning you over, Moo.
True!
Sheesh,
this is so classic.
The timing couldn't be more perfect.
Moo,
you're finally going to be free from him.
Man, I'm happy!
Yeah!
- Woo!
I'm happy...
I'm so happy...
Whoa, look.
What a glowing skin.
- Here, let me have a look.
- Here.
How the hell did you find him?
I've got skills, you know?
Damn!
Hey, let me take another look.
Look, I'm as tall as you are now.
Moo, this is Gimm.
Gimm, this is Moo.
He's Tai's friend
and also my boy...
Also an intern!
Hello, Moo.
That makes you my senior intern, right?
Please take care of me.
Of course.
Let's be friends, Gimm.
Mm.
Anyway,
please take care of Gimm.
Sure thing, Fu.
Now then...
if you'll excuse me.
Mm.
Bye-bye.
I'm heading out.
- Bye-bye.
- I'm going now.
Right this way.
- Mm, alright.
- I'll advise you on it.
It already looks good.
My face looks so big.
One, two, three.
- Hello, everyone.
- Oh!
- Hello!
This is Gimm, the new intern.
Oh...
Gimm,
Mr. Chalermchai's son, right?
Ooh!
How adorable!
That's right.
Please don't hesitate to
give me any kind of training.
I can do just about anything.
Uh...
I can even make coffee.
Who'd dare have the son
of the hotel's major partner make coffee?
Right?
- We wouldn't.
- That's crazy...
Ooh!
Here's some coffee, guys.
- Go ahead and have some.
- Thank you.
Here's yours, Moo.
There's more for everyone.
Please, feel free to grab one.
That's so adorable of you, Gimm.
I never thought
I'd get to try coffee from this brand.
A blessing to the tongue!
So what are we waiting for?
Drink up!
- Oh, let's go then.
- Hurry now.
Gimm,
you don't have to do all this next time.
- What a rich coffee!
- We have free coffee at the hotel.
- Oh, it's alright.
- The coffee is so good!
I redeemed these
with my credit card points.
Think of it as a treat for my seniors.
Yum.
Gimm,
thank you so much.
I'm totally motivated to work now!
Isn't this whole thing
supposed to be the other way around?
That's correct. Ooh!
Fabulous!
Wanna try this one here?
This one...
That's right.
Moo, I'm done over here.
Is there anything else
you'd like my help with?
I don't think so. We're good.
- Alright.
- Okay.
Let's go, kiddos.
Alright then.
Excuse me, Gimm.
Are you Gimm Gunklao?
That's me.
Can I have a photo with you?
Absolutely.
Gift, could you hold this for me?
Sure.
Thank you.
My face looks big from this angle.
- Would you like me to hold the camera?
- Yes, thank you.
One, two, three.
Speaking of,
I wanna witness a FuGimm moment in person.
Guys,
anyone want to come with me?
Hard pass.
Fu, what the?!
What are you doing?
My Moo-Moo is looking so cute today.
Look how adorable you're dressed.
You even have our hotel's pin on.
You noticed?
I pay attention to every detail of you.
You're way too close.
Someone might see us!
Let them.
I just want to look at you all day.
But we already agreed
that we'd never let
the people at the hotel know
that we are...
Dating?
Mm.
Exactly. No one can find out.
What about Tai and Tee?
Not them either.
We need to wait until the right time.
My Moo-Moo.
I'm so crazy about you I could die!
I can't even tell anyone!
If you can hold out,
I'll give you a treat.
You're bribing me with treats again.
Or do you not want it?
I do...
What's the treat?
What is it?
Not telling ya.
Make sure you can hold out first.
I want it!
Mr. Fu, hello.
Hello.
Hello, there.
Mr. Fu, I've already told you
not to come close.
I haven't showered yet!
Mm, you're right.
Uh...
would you like to head down as well?
- Oh, right...
- Yes, please.
Hey, Moo.
Next time you come to work,
make sure you're nice and showered;
otherwise,
it won't look good for the hotel.
Right...
Goldentime
is designed to be a peaceful and cozy space
where people can escape
the hustle and bustle of city life.
All three buildings were
designed with simplicity in mind.
I agree that this place
should offer both peace
and privacy,
and I do like how
all three buildings face one another.
But I think the side facing the city
shouldn't be completely closed off
because Goldentime
is a hotel,
a mall,
and a wellness center,
all of which...
are already part of city life.
As for the buildings themselves,
I'd still like them to be
in keeping with the city side,
because I want people staying here
to enjoy the vibrancy of city life
while having moments of peace
woven into the experience.
No wonder he graduated
with first-class honors in architecture.
May I?
I'd like to propose a small idea.
If the city-side building uses
alternating clear and opaque glass panels,
I think it would help maintain the atmosphere
while giving guests a sense of privacy.
I think that's a good idea.
Mr. Krit,
on that note,
I'd like you to take this idea
into consideration for the design revision.
Of course, Mr. Fu.
Thank you, everyone, for your time today.
Alright.
Is everything good with Room 8807?
Yes, ma'am.
Checked.
Is everything good with Room 8808?
Yes, ma'am.
Checked.
Room 8809?
All good.
Checked.
Moo?
Wh-What?!
Where did he go?
Moo!
Fu, I'm in the middle of work.
But I miss you.
No one's gonna see us here.
Fu, you're impossible.
You're always whisking me away.
What else can I do?
It's just...
I can't help myself.
[Gimm]
[Call declined]
Yes, Gimm?
Have you arrived?
Okay, okay.
I'm on my way to pick you up.
Okay.
Fu, just go.
I'm going back to work.
Okay then.
I'll see you soon.
Come on.
[gimgunklao started following you]
[Follow back]
[Following]
Tee,
why do you and I
have to follow that Little Chicken?
His name is Jeab.
At least call him properly.
Only I can call him by that name.
I've claimed it.
Hey, Jeab's gone!
Whoa, follow him!
[Japanese Writing Practice for Beginners]
How much are these two?
400 baht.
Okay, I'll scan to pay.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Sir, I'll have the same books
as that boy from earlier.
The boy from earlier?
No need for a bag.
Man, pay for me.
Whoa... Tee!
Take these. I don't need them anymore.
What the fuck, man?
Fine, I'll take them.
Hey, did you scream like I did last night?
[#FUUUGIMM as a ship FTW]
It's the hashtag
'FUUUGIMM,' that is!
[Gimm's Fu]
It's Mr. Fu, or Dong Qingshan,
the owner of a luxury hotel,
and Gimm,
the son of a renowned mall owner.
They're working together,
and they look like such a great couple.
It's totally a match made in heaven.
Every day, they're hustling.
Everyday, I'm hustling
Ugh, my shipper's heart!
Argh!
Are they canon?
I bet they are!
A ship, my butt!
- Us shippers!
- We're giggling!
Hashtag...
[#FUUUGIMM as a ship FTW]
"FuGimm."
Ooh, looks like...
my brother is really invested in Gimm.
As he should, right?
Look how adorable he is!
I would've been the same if it were me!
You know, lately,
my brother's been so happy.
I don't know what's gotten into him.
It's like he's madly in love or something.
Look, look!
Yeah, that's cute.
I bet it's because of Gimm.
I bet it is.
Our plan is about to work out.
Wow...
Nice.
Nice, fabulous, and then some...
Speaking of,
I wanna witness a FuGimm moment in person.
Guys,
anyone want to come with me?
Hard pass.
Didn't you say you weren't coming, hm?
Well, I was free.
I didn't have anything better to do,
so I came.
- Wow...
- Mm...
Tai,
you're a fucking beast for this.
Gotta give it to you
when it comes to other people's business.
You never disappoint.
And how did you find out
Gimm was coming here?
I'm still his brother.
Did you forget that?
I have tons of intel.
You don't have to treat me, actually.
Whoa,
of course I do,
or else Uncle Chalermchai's gonna say
I'm being too hard on his son.
Mr. Chalermchai is chill...
Sheesh...
That angle...
is putting my mind in the gutter.
Hey!
Moo!
- What?
- What...
Come on, man.
Thank you.
Is your phone okay?
Hm...
I think it's fine.
Uh, hi.
My name is Tian.
I'm a big fan of FuGimm!
I'm so happy to see this
with my own eyes.
My name is Tai.
Do you remember me?
What are you doing here, Tai?
Hm?
Hello,
Tai,
Tian,
and Moo.
Aw, how cute!
You remember our names!
Now that
everyone is here,
let's eat together.
We've ordered lots of food.
Come on, have a seat, Moo.
- Oh, sure...
- Come on!
Join us.
- Come on, sit next to me.
- Let's eat together.
Excuse me, could we have another chair?
Grab. Me. The spoon.
Fine, fine.
Ugh.
Alright...
- There it is.
- Wow.
Wow...
I think you're gonna like this, Fu.
This restaurant is so famous.
Thank you.
A FuGimm moment!
Wow!
Here's yours, Tian.
This is for you, Tai.
Thank you.
The last piece blesses you
with a handsome boyfriend.
It's for you, Moo.
Let's dig in.
I've been here with
my father many times.
- Okay then.
- Come on now.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's dig in.
Uh... Here's watermelon juice
for Fu's Moo-Moo.
May I ask who that is?
Oh...
He is Moo.
Alright.
Thank you.
- It's "Fu's Moo-Moo"!
Better dig in,
or it's gonna get cold.
Tian,
grab me the spoon.
I can't reach it.
What the hell, man?
Grab it yourself
or just ask for a new one.
You need to!
Just do it!
Grab me the spoon!
Grab. Me. The spoon.
Fine, fine.
Ugh.
Shit...
FuGimm...
just sank.
It's back to...
FuMoo again.
What's wrong with you guys?
Nothing, let's just eat.
Yeah, let's... Let's just eat.
Don't ruin it for them!
There goes my appetite...
We got dragged along.
What are you gonna eat?
Let me come with you.
Moo, are you and Fu dating?
Noo!!
Uh...
Me dating Fu?
I'm into rugged guys with Thai looks.
Fu has a Chinese look,
so totally not my type.
But are you asking...
because you...
have a crush on Fu?
- Oh...
- Moo,
you old butt!
I need to get home. I have to shit!
Hurry up! Our ride is here!
Alright!
Hurry!
What?
What's going on?
Why does it end on such a cliffhanger?
What's wrong, Gift?
There!
A FuGimm
fanfic?
The amount of heartlessness
this author has is insane!
It ends rights when...
Mr. Fu
is about to kiss Gimm!
And then... Bam!
Ended right there!
Girl,
I'm also shipping them!
Seriously,
they are so cute
and perfect together.
Right?
So you two
are in your own little world, huh?
Send me the source, too!
Oh, sure.
I'll send it to the staff's DM.
Here you go, girl.
Sent.
Look, they also added the hashtag,
"FUUUGIMM!"
Aw, so cute!
[Mr. Hotel Owner, My Intern's Heart Is Trembling]
- Let me check it out.
- I'm squealing.
- Kicking my feet in the air!
- Right?!
Tone it down a notch!
We're at work.
- Ooooh!!
What are you guys talking about?
Nothing at all, Mr. Fu.
Everything is perfectly fine.
I'm done.
My work is done.
That's a beautiful pin.
Does the hotel
give this out to every staff member?
I noticed Moo and Fu
are wearing the same one.
Oh...
It just so happens
that I'm making these
for our staff, anyway.
Isn't it beautiful?
It's just a sample, too.
- It is!
Yes! The colors are so pretty, right?
- Yes!
- Such vivid colors!
Then, may I have one?
- Oooh!
- Aww!
Then...
should I place
an order for the couple... Oops!
I meant, for how many people?
"Couple?!"
FuGimm as a couple!
Moo!
Mm!
We barely get our alone time these days.
Of course.
You're always out
on a construction site with Gimm.
How would we have time to meet?
What's with that grin?
I'm just happy.
About what?
Well,
I'm happy that
you're jealous.
Me? Jealous?
Who told you that?
Are you just imagining things?
You could say that,
but I
want you to know this one thing.
No matter who approaches me
or anything of that sort,
you...
will still be my omelet.
Because you stir my heart.
Flabbergasted, huh?
This is called...
Double the kiss!
One more time?
- A mosquito! A mosquito!
- Oh, a mosquito.
- A mosquito!
- A mosquito...
- A mosquito. A chonky one.
- A mosquito.
A chonky one!
Jang,
please spread the word to the team
that not a single mosquito is to be allowed...
in this room!
Of course, I'm on it!
Thank you.
Mosquito...
There it is. Mosquito...
- Mosquito...
- It's a chonky one.
These are the documents
you need to sign before signing off
on the Goldentime design.
Thank you very much.
Your coffee with one sugar and one creamer
is ready, sir.
So no hidden agenda, huh?
No,
not at all.
Aw, does it hurt, Fu?
Your cheek is all red.
Really?
Where?
Right here.
I'm all bruised...
Can you put some remedy on it?
- You want me to?
- Mm.
By smooching my cheek, I meant.
Look,
if you smooch my cheek,
would you believe
all the bruises
would disappear like they were never there.
So extra.
I mean it.
Do you know
that...
you're the best remedy in my life?
But I'm not a remedy.
It's just a smooch on the cheek...
Can't you do that for me?
Otherwise,
my cheek is gonna hurt
for a whole week.
Ow, it hurts.
- Ow, ow, ow...
- Alright, alright, alright.
Fine, but just once, though.
Mm.
Mm!
That...
is a jumbo kiss.
Why are you here by yourself?
I was just lonely.
If that were the case...
you wouldn't have to come all this way.
Is there something on your mind
that made you come all the way out here?
Well, I'm a bit sad.
I ran into my ex,
whom I never thought I'd see again.
And so?
My friend came over.
Your friend?
Right now?
Mm.
What is this, Kluayhom?
- This is gonna spice things up.
- What about everything until now?
Have you been seeing me
at the same time as him?
I don't see what's wrong with it.
I'm not serious with anyone.
Well...
it reminds me of all those awful things
he did to me.
But what's funny is,
right now,
what I'm doing
is no different from what he did.
People stray sometimes.
But now that you've realized it,
it's a good thing, right?
So...
what about what you're doing now?
Well...
I'm not particularly fond of it.
You know?
No one actually listens
or pays attention to me at all.
Most of the time,
they just want to get laid.
Though last night,
we didn't really talk much.
So...
Do you like it
or not?
So...
do you like it or not?
Your writing
looks a lot better today.
This says, "Uru," right?
Uh-huh.
That's it for today, then.
Alright.
Goodbye,
Yu-sensei.
Mm, get home safe.
Alright.
Uh, hi.
Are you interested
in taking a Japanese class?
Pardon?
I saw that you were
looking at us so many times,
so I was wondering if you're interested
in taking Japanese classes with Mr. Yu.
Mr. Yu...
Right!
Is he a good teacher?
Oh, he's really good.
He's probably
the best teacher I've ever had.
Wow, kid.
What are you, a salesperson?
I'm not.
So...
please take Mr. Yu into consideration.
Excuse me.
What's going on,
Mr. and Mrs. Dong?
My dear eldest son,
[Mama]
I've seen stuff about you and Gimm.
How are things?
Tell Papa and me everything!
Ugh, it's nothing, Mama.
He's just here for a summer internship.
Are you sure it's nothing?
But I do think
he's an adorable young man.
Mr. Chalermchai himself
is also quite fond of you.
Right, darling?
Mm, Fu.
Treat Gimm nicely.
Our business is going well
because of them.
And theirs is doing well
because of us too.
Regardless, Fu,
take good care of Gimm.
Moo, watch out!
I made sure
to finish my work so I could
come watch a movie with you.
Excuse me, are you Mr. Fu?
Oh, I am.
So...
Is Gimm not here with you today?
No, he's not.
- Let's just go.
- Mm.
- What?
- Girl...
- Who is he here with, anyway?
- No clue.
They're probably fans of FuGimm.
Fu, you're all famous now.
You have to be more careful from now on.
Don't worry about someone else.
Let's take this time
to enjoy our movie.
[#UndertheCEOsDesk: No idea who Fu
locked arms with, but he's def not our Gimm.]
[Guys, can you help me take a look;
am I seeing things,
or is it actually over for #FUUUGIMM?]
- Whoa!
- Here, here.
Have you read the new BossNoeul fanfic?
There's a new one?!
- Yeah!
- Ooh...
Is it heavenly?
- Is it?
- Very!
I was digging into my pillow.
Let me see...
Hello, guys.
Uh... Here.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh!
- Right?
Girls, the views are insane!
Ooh!
Come on, let's see...
Can I jump right into reading?
Guys, hello.
- Oh, hi there!
- Hello.
Aw!
- Here are some snacks.
- Oh, that's an armful!
I've bought some snacks for everyone.
- Thank you.
- Aw, thank you!
- This one's mine!
- Ooh, ooh, ooh.
That's so nice of you
to treat us to snacks,
unlike some intern here, right?
Huh...
Right?
Thank you.
You shouldn't have.
Moo,
wanna join us?
- Can I take some of these home?
- Go ahead. I'm...not hungry just yet.
Eat well, guys.
- Sure thing. How nice
- There's enough for us all.
Oh, that one looks good, wanna trade?
Moo, watch out!
I'm sorry.
Be more careful next time.
I'm sorry, Mr. Fu. I really am.
Moo?
Are you alright?
You've been zoning out lately.
I'm fine.
Here, let me see.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine, really.
I'm going back to work.
Huh!
No space for a third person.
Moo, come sit with me.
How delusional.
Jang,
what's going on here?
Don't worry about it.
These damn girls
are bonkers.
They got too invested.
I just...don't understand what I did wrong.
If I did something wrong, you can tell me.
It's not about that, Moo.
So...
you know how these girls
are fans of Mr. Fu and Gimm, right?
Lately, someone posted
photos of you and Mr. Fu
while you were, like,
watching a movie,
and...
Mr. Fu and Gimm just so happened
to become distant lately,
so these damn girls
just...
thought
Mr. Fu was having an affair with you.
Huh?!
I'm having an affair?!
Yeah!
Hey,
I will
report everyone
who reads
fanfiction during work hours.
Moo...
Moo,
don't... Don't slap me... Argh!
I was just kidding.
Sometimes, I got, like,
too carried away while reading.
I never meant to make you overthink it,
truly.
Gift,
I'm not overthinking it.
If it's about work, don't hesitate
to lecture me if I make a mistake,
but...
if it's about the fictions you read...
don't slap me.
I'm scared.
I'm not letting this go.
Don't!
No... Ow!
Ow!
Moo, are you and Fu dating?
Are you asking...
because you...
have a crush on Fu?
Girl,
I'm also shipping them!
Seriously,
they are so cute
and perfect together.
Right?
So...
Is Gimm not here with you today?
[Mr. Hotel Owner, My Intern's Heart Is Trembling]
No, he's not.
- Who is he here with, anyway?
- No clue.
That's so nice of you
to treat us to snacks,
unlike some intern here, right?
Right?
Thank you.
What?
Moo's getting banned?
That's right, Mr. Fu.
Some people are just too caught up in fiction.
Good thing I'm Team...
FuMoo!
Ryan,
I think I need your help.
What's going on?
Mr. Fu has never
called a gathering like this before.
Mm, right?
- Girl...
- Is something wrong?
Hm?
Not a clue!
Don't hide it.
Suspish.
What's going on?!
- Do you know?
- I don't, girl. I don't.
Hello, everyone.
I would like to thank everyone
for taking the time to be here.
I won't take too much of it.
I want the atmosphere at our hotel
to be family-like
and warm, like it always has been.
I always shared
my experience with my seniors,
my juniors,
and all of the staff
in a friendly manner.
There's one thing
I'd like to share with everyone.
Moo and I
are in a relationship.
Huh?!
- Huh?!
- Oooh!
Surprise!
When, though?
Shocker.
Uh...
Oh my, oh my!
Goodness...
Thank you for giving me
a chance to intern here, Fu.
No problem, Gimm.
Well,
we'll likely cross paths again in the future.
Though...
there's one thing I want you to help with.
Mm, what is it?
So...
I...
I'm thinking about...
making my relationship with Moo public.
Would it be okay
for you to talk to the fans about it?
I don't want to see Moo sad anymore.
Mm,
you can trust me on that.
I'll handle it, no problem.
Thank you so much, Gimm.
Fu,
you're really madly in love.
Moo,
everyone knows
that we're together already.
Shocker.
I'm having a heart attack.
Hey,
you guys already knew?
- Duh!
- Huh?!
- Papa is coming back tomorrow?!
Or maybe...
this is about
the new son-in-law of the Dong family?
That Lhee girl,
is she really that terrifying?
Moo's sister
is so damn brutal!
You opportunist!
How dare you
get handsy with my little brother?!
You're dead!!
Get ready.
I'll win your heart in
three...
two...
one...
♫I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart♫
♫Add another hundred
♫Even when you're ready to leap,♫
♫I'll always be ready to love♫
♫I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart♫
♫Again, you're running from me♫
♫Following you around
is making me lonely♫
♫Again, you're mad at me,♫
♫But why do you have to look so lovely?♫
♫Oh Baby♫
♫Told me not to love, but I already fell♫
♫Told me not to follow,
but you've attracted me so well♫
♫Baby, I'm crush on ya♫
♫I need a way to flirt with you, yeah♫
♫I have a hundred tricks
to win, win your heart♫
♫Add another hundred
♫Even when you're ready to leap,♫
♫I'll always be ready to love♫
♫I'll use a hundred more tricks
to win, win your heart♫